When you're developing a multi- aent
system for your software development
life cycle, you can have multi-coding
agents all of them writing code in
parallel or sequential and you need to
decide how you want to do that. You can
have a diversity of agent with different
roles. So roughly speaking there's
multiple consideration you need to have.
There are certain tasks that are super
repeatable, super automatable where you
can get just another level of
automation, another level of
productivity boost by, you know, running
multiple agents in the cloud to take
down these like very automatable tech
oriented tasks.
>> Is there value in saying I'm going to
use different models, different agents,
different vendors of agents in terms of
doing different roles?
So I think some people when they're
thinking about different agents the
first like thing pops into mind some
people is like okay I give it a
different prompt or something like that
>> that that architecture is basically like
an architecture of uh one single agent
that rules them all that all you need to
do is give it different tools and uh and
and and different like prompt or or so.
Uh that's one option. Uh the other
option is that agents are much more
different than that. For example, their
entire architecture, their graph of how
they build might be completely
different. For example, if you're doing
if you're dealing with a coding agent,
then in order to really do its job like
it's actually at least until now proven
that you need to enable it creativity.
Yeah. Because we developers, we bump
into a lot of issues and we bypass them
this and that like and actually the fact
that core is an LLM making the decision
is a good architecture for a coding
agent at least what we're seeing for
example in Sweepbenge if you're familiar
>> and then when you're talking about other
types of agent for example you want to
have a security agent or you want to
have a code review agent that agent
might want to have actually much more
structure checking A B C D for example
you might have like 100 rules that's how
do you get them with subtopic we can
talk about you want to have 100 rules
that you want to make sure that are
obeyed and then you want that agent that
review agent to be much much more struct
like structured there is an LLM there
but the graph of that agent might be
like uh 1 to 10 there where LLM is
involved but actually it's quite quite
structured there so and and by the way
you might give it different permissions
etc so so overall like there's a
discussion do you have one agent the
rules at all or multiple uh multiple
agents what we're seeing of course like
when you're jiggling dealing with
enterprisegrade
heavyduty brown field when compliance
standardization etc. you must have like
different agents that are completely
different than each other,
>> different vendors. So maybe like I don't
know a claude code or sorry Claude or
something like that. Do you find like
that will be better in a specific role?
So like is there is there a specific
vendor that is best for code reviews or
or security testing like you said? Yeah,
actually it's a good like uh point to to
continue from my last point where
>> different vendors have different DNA and
different like point of view on the
world like on on entropic believe at
least what I understand is that models
everything
>> and you need to give that model the
brain of everything and you need to give
them like agents in order to operate in
the world these tools needs to be quite
simple actually on the fly why do you
need to start doing retrieval augmented
generation just give it a simple tool
like ASD grap etc that's actually pretty
good like uh I I believe uh uh let's say
structure and and way of thinking for
coding agents. Yeah. But then when you
look under review security review agent
if you're familiar like three four five
months ago what all the rage and you l
took a look on the prompt
>> you are now a security review agent and
then there is a prompt and then there is
like a list of exclusion don't look at
DOS don't look on that
>> like basically it's when you're doing a
security agent you need one plus of one
minus of that
>> you here is everything that you need to
check rigorously and then you can be
creative on all the rest
>> when you're If you encode your encoding
agent, you want to relax this and say
what what not. But when you're doing a
re security agent, then actually you
need to do a one minus of what they're
doing. Yeah.
>> So I would use their their uh cloud code
for example as a vendor when you're
talking about cloud code as code coding
agent. Uh but I don't think it's like
you can just set up with a different
prompt to to to be like all all type of
agents out there. You need a different
vendor.
>> Absolutely. Absolutely. Uh and very
briefly because I see people people are
kicking out now so it might get a bit
noisy but very very briefly in terms of
context like security is a great example
where there are there's a ton of context
that you can provide an agent say look
here are your rules this is what you
have to check for at what point does at
what point where uh does the task that
you give an agent just become so
overwhelming it starts doing a poor job
security review is a great example code
review maybe even with you know a large
number of styling rules and those types
of things where's the limit for that
>> yeah context is extremely important you
know I can superlative context is the
king the kingdom
>> uh etc. But it's extremely important
actually I talked about it that uh
developers reports that 33 to 80 80%
depends on which uh tech and and how you
ask it think that context is actually
the major problem of of bad quality and
hallucination and something like that
and that's your number one request from
coding agent to to improve the thing is
that context is not just one thing it's
not just a code base it could be for
example a database of vulnerabilities it
could be for example kodto is the
leading code review tool for example we
have a database related to best
practices and rules that we project
depending on the stack of that what you
have etc and we learn it from different
like interaction with developers in the
context engine. So we collect a database
that related to best practices and rules
and then like it's really like you
really need to fetch the right the right
context and and then it's it's not just
um like when you're thinking about
context on one hand it is like
>> you have too much not accurate
>> the like the other is like exactly only
what you need in the middle for example
it could be like uh a lot of uh
nonrelevant but all the relevant etc.
Yeah.
>> So, so it's kind of a spectrum and of
course uh like the one of the hardest
thing is actually bringing the right
context and and then what we see the
hardest bringing the right context and
then making sure it's only that there
these are these are the priorities and
then that could define a lot for example
as I mentioned security companies might
have context relevant for security that
regular coding agent do not have code
review uh solution like codto might have
additional context that is relevant to
best practice standard etc that regular
coding agent don't That's how the way I
look at it. How do you bring the right
context and then cut that you don't have
too much because there is like the the
context rot if you want to read more
about it that's like entropic and other
company talk about the context rot.
Yeah, super super interesting and but
yeah, so correct as so so right as well
because context giving too much context
you think okay I've got all these rules
that I need to follow you throw it all
in one go and actually it's just going
to forget what it wants to forget or
it's not going to add it's not going to
>> I think if I connect all the dots we
talked about context is very important
maybe one of the most important and then
is how you use them when you upload for
example context cloud code or cursor for
them it's like part of the you know
>> part of their like just literally the
context and then they just keep pushing
that in the context in their graph. If
you like give it same prompt with the
same context seven times you get seven
different solutions but but uh so like I
do want to say like context is important
but then how you use it while maybe
other tools will use it very differently
or like in a workflow verifying
different thing etc. So context is
extremely important uh and the I just
want to add on what you're saying not
completely following the context is also
a matter of how you build the agent.
Yeah, absolutely.
>> So that's another point.
>> It's been awesome. It's been awesome
catching up.
>> Hello. Joining me here is Robert
Brennan, who is the CEO of Open Hands.
Robert, good to see you here.
>> Yeah, good to see you as well.
>> And of course, I saw you here, well, not
here, but in New York only a few weeks
ago for AI Native DevCon.
>> Yeah, good to see you again.
>> Yeah, no, likewise.
>> What's your session going to be about
today?
>> So, we're going to be talking about how
to scale code maintenance with AI
agents. Um, I would say there's a lot of
tasks where developers are uh for like
their day-to-day feature development.
They're used to like pairing with cloud
code or the openhand CLI locally on
their laptop. Uh, and that works great
for your like ad hoc work. You know, you
pick up a ticket, you need to work on
it. Uh, but there are certain tasks that
are super repeatable, super automatable
where you can get just another level of
uh automation, another level of
productivity boost by, you know, running
multiple agents in the cloud to take
down these like very automatable tech
oriented uh tasks. Awesome. And and I
guess you know when we talk about
maintenance, what what kind of things
are we talking about? Typical
maintenance tasks that a developer would
do.
>> Yeah. So very typical things would be
things like um like dependency
management uh you know resolving open
source vulnerabilities that happen in
your codebase. Um and then some meteor
tasks like you know maybe upgrading from
Python 2 to Python 3 or upgrading you
know from an old version of Java to a
new version of Java, maybe migrating
from Cobalt to Java or another more
modern programming language. Uh there's
a lot of these like toiley tasks that
developers don't really like doing. They
don't involve a lot of creativity or
critical thinking. Uh it's mostly just a
lot of like churning out lines of code.
Um but they're still too big for uh you
know a single agent to oneshot in many
cases.
>> U and so uh doing what we call agent
orchestration uh can allow you to you
know put some forethought into how
you're going to solve this repeatable
problem in a way that can scale across
many code bases. uh and then just uh you
know automate it 90% of the way there uh
and just have a human in the loop for
you know the very little bit where you
need that last uh last bit of
verification.
>> So let's talk about agent orchestration
then. So when we talk about agent
orchestration we're obviously talking
about multiple agents. Do they have to
be the same agent or can they just be
different vendors that that kind of
thing?
>> Yeah, I think it's it's helpful to be
working within like a single agent
framework, right? Uh there's nothing
necessarily stopping, you know, one
agent from talking to another agent. Um
and there are you know there's the ADA
protocol and things like that. Um, but
what we've tried to build with the open
hands SDK is like a single framework
that allows you to create multiple
multiple different agents with like
different system prompts, different sets
of tools that they have access to, uh,
different MCP servers that they have
access to. Um, and you know, maybe
different um, behavior patterns, right?
>> Um, and then getting those agents
talking to each other is uh, you know,
it gives you kind of like a single
framework for thinking about how to uh,
you know, coordinate multiple agents
together,
>> right? And when we think about when we
start with kind of like a large task
typically that a number of agents can
can all work on um we don't obviously
just throw that large task at all these
agents group of agents we need to break
that task down. Exactly. What's the
process of kind of breaking that down?
Is there is there amount of human
interaction in that or can we uh
somewhat automate that for AI as well?
>> Yeah, I think that's that's kind of the
the most critical step is like how are
you going to break this problem down
into sub pieces that individual agents
can execute on? Right.
>> Um so I think that's where the most
human thought goes into the process. Uh
but you can you know work with uh you
know an LLM like Claude for instance to
kind of talk through the problem and uh
help like get get some help from uh an
LLM to break down the problem into
manageable by bite-sized tasks. But
you're also going to have to really lean
on your own intuition for what is
actually solvable. Uh what's reviewable
by a human? You know what what can you
give to the agent that you can then look
at on the other end when it when it
gives you some output and quickly verify
did it do the thing or did it not.